vcricket.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy - Read on to know about the online privacy policy of vcricket.com

Revision - v1.1 - 25th November, 2010.  
(added to v1.0)

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

\--------------------------------------  
Revision - v1.0 - 10th september, 2006.

Our privacy policy covers all personally identifiable information which is or has been collected when you visit vcricket.com or use our services.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to any Partner site and services supplied by our partners.

We collect information in various ways from users, namely:

Personal information is collected when users register for the site as a whole or for particular services. like forums, competitions, special offers, user services or surveys.  
We collect basic information including Name, eMail addresses and other preference details to help customize our services for the users.  
We record IP addresses and use cookies for analytic's and geo-targeting content.  
WE WOULD NOT RESELL OR RENT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANYONE.

We may share aggregate data to Partners, Sponsors and potential advertisers, which may not disclose any personal information. These data would be shared for customizing our services to the user.

We would always inform the user, when the details would be shared with the partners.

WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USER INFORMATION PROVIDED AT THIRD PARTY PARTNERS SITE.

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect users' personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to it or from its online products or services, and users do so at their own risk.

We are not responsible for voluntarily disclosure of personal information online in our public displayed services.

We do not promote our services to children under the age of 13.

If there is is a change in privacy policy, we will post the changes here and would also notify to the user if there is a change in the policy.
